[{"id": 17, "text": "Format : MAC Report", "label": [[9, 12, "MISC"]]}, {"id": 18, "text": "Sl.No\tOriginator/ Ref No.\t\t Gist of Input \t\tAction Taken", "label": []}, {"id": 19, "text": "1.\tDIA", "label": [[3, 6, "ORG"]]}, {"id": 20, "text": "March 18, 2018", "label": [[0, 14, "DATE"]]}, {"id": 21, "text": "I:437428", "label": []}, {"id": 22, "text": "\tThuraya Activity", "label": [[1, 8, "MISC"]]}, {"id": 23, "text": "ID-NA (IMEI NO :Not Available)", "label": []}, {"id": 24, "text": "Active at 35Â° 52' 38\" N,003Â° 84' 99\" E about 8.1 Km SE of Rawala Kot, 10.4 Km NW of Helan (POK) & 23.4 Km outside from LC on 18 Mar 18 at 0740 hrs (GPS Age:02 Mins).(Location Update).    \tShared with HQ _____ Comd & HQ ___ Corps on March 18, 2018 by DIA.", "label": [[10, 23, "LATITUDE"], [24, 38, "LONGITUDE"], [45, 51, "MEASUREMENT"], [52, 54, "DIRECTION"], [58, 68, "LOC"], [70, 77, "MEASUREMENT"], [78, 80, "DIRECTION"], [84, 89, "LOC"], [91, 94, "LOC"], [98, 105, "MEASUREMENT"], [119, 121, "MISC"], [125, 134, "DATE"], [138, 146, "TIME"], [200, 202, "MISC"], [232, 246, "DATE"], [250, 253, "ORG"]]}, {"id": 25, "text": "Ser No\tOriginator/ Ref No.\t\t Gist of Input \t\tAction Taken", "label": []}, {"id": 26, "text": "1.\t\tAgency", "label": [[4, 10, "MISC"]]}, {"id": 27, "text": "Date", "label": []}, {"id": 28, "text": "Msg ID", "label": []}, {"id": 29, "text": "\tType of Activity", "label": []}, {"id": 30, "text": "Details of Activity", "label": []}, {"text": "NW of Helan", "label": [[6, 10, "LOC"]]}, {"text": "BSF website was hacked by Bangladeshi hackers in retaliation", "label": [[0, 2, "ORG"]]}, {"text": "Haripur Upazila in Thakurgaon District", "label": [[0, 14, "LOC"]]}, {"text": "and how we were guided by sir Anupam Bera", "label": [[30, 40, "PERSON"]]}, {"text": "From the Central Institute of Technology in Kokrajhar", "label": [[9, 39, "ORG"]]}, {"text": "Human Rights Watch (HRW) issued an 81-page report which alleged ", "label": [[0, 18, "ORG"]]}, {"text": "NW of Helan ", "label": [[6, 10, "LOC"]]}, {"text": "One of the leading banking companies of the New Zealand Government", "label": [[44, 54, "LOC"]]}, {"text": "Migration of BPM Applications", "label": [[13, 15, "ORG"]]}, {"text": "BSF website was hacked by Bangladeshi", "label": [[0, 2, "ORG"]]}, {"text": "BSF website was hacked by", "label": [[0, 2, "ORG"]]}, {"text": "The United LOC States of America (U.S.A. or USA), commonly known as the LOC United LOC States (U.S. or US) or America", "label": [[-1, 22, "LOC"]]}, {"text": "45° 10′ 11″ E at the centre of the globe", "label": [[0, 12, "LONGITUDE"]]}, {"text": "Email- hariom12@gmail.com", "label": [[7, 24, "EMAIL"]]}, {"text": "Email- hariom12@gmail.com", "label": [[7, 24, "EMAIL"]]}, {"text": "hariom12@gmail.com", "label": [[0, 17, "EMAIL"]]}, {"text": "The United States emerged from the Thirteen British Colonies", "label": [[35, 59, "ORG"]]}, {"text": "Bangladesh government and Bangladeshi organizations protested", "label": [[0, 9, "LOC"]]}, {"text": "BSF has been compelled to act tough against Bangladeshi", "label": [[0, 2, "ORG"]]}]